Sergey Maslinikov

2696264040 | maslinikovsergey@gmail.com | Dallsa, TX

Summary

5 years of total experience in QA & Software Developer. I have a positive outlook on things, and always ready to learn new methods. I work well both independently and as a team.

Portfolio: https://sergimasl.github.io/portfolio_v_2/

GitHub: https://github.com/SergiMasI

Experience

Infosys | Dallas, TX

Software Support Engineer | 06/2022 - Present

UI & UX Dev, support oracle database & QA testing.

Revature

Junior Full Stuck Developer | 12/2021 - 06/2022

Development frontend and backend on Java/Spring and Angular. Auto testing in Java.

Loci Properties | Kalamazoo, MI Frontend Developer | 05/2021 - 01/2022

Part-time frontend development. QA testing.

Skills

React.js, Java, C#, JavaScript, Sass (Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets), Spring Framework, CSS, Test Automation, MySQL

Education

Kemerovo State University | Kemerovo, KO Physics

Kalamazoo Valley Community College | Portage, MI Biological Sciences

Western Michigan University | Kalamazoo, MI Biomedical Sciences